Register of the Wisconsin. Governor: Governors' Messages to the Legislature, 1848-1856, 1868-1921
Wisconsin Historical Society
Wisconsin. Governor: Governors' Messages to the Legislature, 1848-1856, 1868-1921
Wisconsin. Governor
Series 118
2.0 c.f. (1 record center carton, 2 archives boxes, and 2 volumes)
Wisconsin Historical Society, Library-Archives Division
Outgoing handwritten and typed letters to the Legislature, including letters concerning prisoners paroled, lists of signed bills deposited with the Secretary of State, veto messages, and nominations. The years from 1857 to 1867 are missing. The text of some formal messages to the Legislature and veto messages is included, but the bulk of material is much more routine. Volumes 4, 5, and 9-12 are indexed alphabetically by subject.
Administrative/Restriction Information
Volume 14 was added from Series 141.
Contents List
- 1848-1856, Series 118 (Volume 1)
- 1868 January 15-1870 March 14 (Box 1, Volume 2)
- 1870 March 15-1873 March 18 (Box 1, Volume 3)
- 1873 March 19-1878 June 7 (Box 1, Volume 4)
- 1879 January 21-1887 April 7 (Box 1, Volume 5)
- 1887 April 5-1891 April 23 (Box 1, Volume 6)
- 1891 April 23-1893 April 21 (Box 1, Volume 7)
- 1895 January 17-1896 February 28 (Box 1, Volume 8)
- 1897 January 25-August 20 (Box 1, Volume 9)
- 1899 January 20-1905 June 9 (Volume 10)
- 1905 June 21-1911 January 1 (Box 1, Volume 11)
- 1911 January 12-1915 January 4 (Box 2, Volume 12)
- 1915 January 14-1920 December 31 (Box 2, Volume 13)
- 1921 January 18-July 14 (Box 3, Volume 14)